You failed.
Instead of bringing the Uranus Queen to us as instructed,
you allowed her to awaken.
I apologize, Master.
You have failed us for the last time, Beta.
Those insects have never come close to finding the synops.
After several thousand years, what purpose does she serve?
The electronic warfare class Angeloid is obsolete.
Wait! Don't do that!
I'll get her next time, I promise!
What can you possibly do to take down the Uranus Queen
now that she's awakened?
Wait a moment.
I have an idea.
I am so horrifyingly bored,
being up here.
Entertain me.
Whatever you ask of me, Master!
I imagine that.
During the age of discovery,
there was a setback aboard the ship on which Columbus was sailing.
His sailors were having doubts about their long journey
and in their despair attempted a mutiny.
I see.
So Columbus lied to them.
He entered a much shorter journey into the ship's log
than the real figures of which he was perfectly aware.
Having believed these figures, the men continued their journey,
and that crew is said to have eventually discovered the new world.
You could actually say...
You could say it's a tale that started with a lie.
A tale of the discovery of the new world.
Nikako, just what are you doing?
Well, clearly I'm your assistant.
Weren't you looking for a new one?
I figured you'd be lonely all by yourself,
so I thought I'd come help you out some.
I'm pretty number three at your service.
It's the perfect weather for a barbecue.
Holy crap!
This place is swimming with people.
Over here!
A few of my men are holding down a spot for us nearby.
And look!
In the shade!
Hey, Tomiki?
Nymph hasn't come back yet, has she?
No, not yet.
She's probably back visiting her homeland up in the sky.
Jeez, what a load.
She drops in out of nowhere then vanishes into thin air.
We should start setting everything up.
Hang on, where's Icarus?
Don't do that, lady! You'll break it!
Icarus!
What are you doing over here, you idiot?
Sorry about that, sir.
I'll pay for the whole thing.
How much are we talking about?
No freaking way!
This is huge!
This is that legendary DVD,
the ridiculously perverted one with all the bouncy goodness!
The Age of Warring Boobs, G-Cup Rebellion!
It's nothing short of a miracle that I found this sucker here!
Of all places!
I'll, uh...
I'll take this.
No tears!
Excuse me, Master.
I'm sorry that happened.
I need to act normal.
I have to find a way to be more like the humans I know.
Little Miss Weapon of Death!
But how?
How do humans act?
I can't believe you said that!
Oh, come on.
It's only human to lie.
That's terrible!
So you've lied to me.
To act human is to lie.
Welcome back, Tomaki!
And Icarus!
The meat will be done soon!
To act human is to lie.
Um, Sohara?
Yeah?
What's up?
I just wanted you to know that I hate you.
No one thinks you're cute.
In fact, everyone thinks you're quite unattractive.
You appear to be kind, but you're actually a very violent person.
But why?
I also think you're just a little too skinny.
And that's a bad thing?
Anyway, I just wanted to let you know.
Those are the reasons I hate you as much as I do.
The new world doesn't exist, Sugata.
And Prez, you're...
I'm what?
You're a very nice person.
Oh, stop.
You're making me blush.
I don't get it!
That's the opposite of what you said about me!
And as for you, Tomoki, I don't want to be with you anymore.
I don't want to be with you anymore.
Is this crap the best you can cook?
I thought I was a good person!
You two are pretty lucky to be able to get drunk off soda.
We're still not even close to old enough to drink,
so we have to find something, don't we?
I don't think it's something to be this upset over.
I just can't help it.
No one has ever talked to me like that before.
Icarus is such a beating!
Well then, by all means, drink yourself stupid.
Icarus didn't vanish,
and Icarus doesn't want to be with me anymore.
This sucks.
Everybody's just doing whatever the hell they want.
Damn!
I need something to take my mind off this crap,
cause if not, it's gonna drive me nuts!
The takoyaki you're serving looks like poop on a stick.
You've got a beautiful thick head of hair.
Your baby is uglier than you are.
Finally, I'm acting human.
You look like you're having a good time, Alpha.
Hello, Nymph.
What are you doing here?
Wanna do me a favor and disable your Artemis lock-on?
Cause if you don't, those missile alarms ringing in my head
are gonna drive me up the nearest wall.
I'm not here to tell people who you really are.
Nothing like that.
And it's not like I could ever beat you in battle,
so you can relax a bit, girl.
Don't worry.
I just wanna see what's happening on my soap opera.
Maybe hang around a little longer, you know?
Sure.
Tell me, Alpha.
Don't you think you're a bit subservient to your new master down here?
These stupid bugs are just trash to us.
They're nothing.
I still don't get what you're trying to do.
But unless you wanna destroy your relationship with him,
don't even mention what happened between you and me.
Hmph.
Fooled her completely.
She has no clue the only reason I'm here is to take her back.
Peace Stealth System, activate.
I will follow my master's orders.
Even though I've got no way to outstrip her firepower,
I'm gonna take her back into the sky with me.
But to achieve that, I gotta do something else first.
I'm taking her precious master hostage.
See how she likes that.
So sorry, Alpha.
You think that's enough to keep out of sight?
Because I can see you.
Wait!
What?
How is this possible?
You gotta try harder to keep from my prying eyes.
I can see freaking everything.
That's the stuff, baby.
Yeah, do it!
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm watching people do it?
Nothing like a live show to cheer me up.
Since I can't afford the DVD...
Wait.
Who's there?
Nope?
What are those two people doing?
It looks like the woman is taking off her clothes.
Don't look!
And where the hell have you been, huh?
You've freaking vanished into thin air!
You can't pull that crap!
Whatever.
Who cares?
I care, dummy!
If you're gonna leave, at least let me know first.
You have any idea how much I've been worrying about you?
You've been worried?
Of course I have!
I mean, sure, you're a self-centered freeloader, but that doesn't mean you can just disappear without telling anybody!
Yeah, okay.
Hang on!
I'm here to take him hostage, not get ordered around.
What am I doing listening to him?
Good.
Now, as punishment, you have to do everything I tell you today.
Understand me?
Now, let's go.
You're coming with me.
Uh, no!
Wait!
So, what are you doing again?
Huh?
Can't you tell by looking?
There's a flea market going on.
I'm setting up a booth.
I need that DVD, but I'm flat broke.
Therefore, my brilliant plan is to sell off all my old crap.
And then the boobies will be mine!
I'm a freaking genius!
You think this junk will sell?
Maybe.
That's why I needed someone to help me out.
So, here's what you do.
Get out there and attract some customers.
What?
What are the two of you up to?
Um, hey, guys!
Nymph!
Good to see you again!
Icarus told us you'd come back.
We would have missed you if you hadn't.
I'm so glad.
So, welcome back!
Yeah, thanks, I guess.
It looks like you're running a booth.
But I honestly don't think any of this stuff is gonna sell.
You don't know that!
Oh, come on.
This could be fun.
I've always wanted to try my hand at retail.
Hey, Icarus, let's you and I run a booth!
Come one, come all!
Get your bellies filled with Icarus' delicious lunches!
Our shop is an enormous success, Icarus!
The two of us make a great combo!
If you say so, Sahara.
So, uh, all that stuff you said to me before,
you know, about hating me and all?
That's right, I totally hate you.
That's what I thought!
There's your everyday Tommy gun,
or your Colt M1911 pistol.
But of course, they're all non-working replicas.
Aw, damn it.
Jerks are stealing all of my customers.
Well, Sagata, not so much, of course.
Nymph, you're gonna have to help me out somehow.
I want that DVD more than anything!
I'm not doing anything else.
Guess I'll help.
Really? You will?
When you get the DVD, can I watch it too?
I don't know.
Tell you what, instead, if we make some decent cash,
I'll buy you whatever you want.
Whatever I want?
Suppose that could work.
And I just gotta help you, right?
Sure, that sounds easy enough.
Thanks a million, Nymph.
You know, this stuff you're trying to sell is pretty crappy.
Why don't you open up a food booth like Alpha did?
Like Okonomiyaki, maybe?
Makes sense.
People always like to eat.
Great value! Top quality!
This is one unique Okonomiyaki!
Check it! Tomaki opened an Okonomiyaki booth.
I'll take one, please, my good sir.
You got it, young lady.
Now, what kind would you like exactly?
Feast your eyes upon our glorious menu!
Tomo, what the hell is that?
For those who prefer them just right, our standard boobies.
For those who like them a little more petite,
try our half-egg boobies.
And for those with the love of the enormous,
our glorious E and F cup boobies!
Toomoki, it looks like all the female customers are ditching you.
Oh, son of a bitch.
Oh.
Why don't you try selling some kind of idol products?
I heard girls like that stuff.
Hell, yeah, great idea.
Ladies and gents,
we've got a killer special for you all today.
It's a Tomoki photo, a Tomoki fan.
And if you buy now, I'll throw in some Tomoki boxers
all for the rock-bottom price of just 200 Yen.
Oh.
No takers?
Well, strike three.
No choice. Time to resort to my back-up plan.
Psst. Hey, mister. Down here, mister.
Check these out.
Got a pair of high school girls' panties here.
Special discount.
You buy now and I'll even toss in a free pick
of the chick who wears them.
What do you say, huh?
Tomoki?
So, Tomoki, you okay there?
Oh, I love y'all.
Hey!
I'm having this terrible crappy day
when all of you are just freakin' perfect, aren't you?
You all think you're so cool and so together,
while I'm yours!
All these cool dudes all over the place
and I feel like a chump.
He keep taking all the hot chicks
and here I am, alone as always.
It sucks. It just sucks.
It's the whole reason I even care about this dumb DVD.
This is about you wanting to be popular with the ladies?
Maybe, but it's not like that's ever going to happen.
Oh, poor guy.
Here you go.
What did you just do to me?
I just gave you the gift of cool guy jamming.
Look over there.
It's already taking effect.
Why are those girls looking at me?
Basically, I used my jamming system
to make all of the women here
see you as their ideal guy.
From the looks on their faces,
it sure seems to be working well.
This is the moment I've been waiting for my whole life!
Now I can show them what a real man is made of!
THE END
Sorry for the wait, ladies,
but your number one has arrived.
Tomoki's here.
Now...
Give me some sugar.
Who's first?
Girls, please. There's enough to share.
Why don't we all enjoy a cocktail first?
Oh, sure. I'll have one.
Oh, me, too. I want a bunch.
I'll have a hundred. Get it drunk, baby.
This is bad. I ended up helping him out.
I'm supposed to be taking the idiot hostage,
not hooking him up with an endless supply of hot women.
What am I doing here?
Nymph, why are you just sitting there?
Move that cute little tail of yours.
Bring us some more drinks, would you?
Okay.
Who wants Dom Perignon?
Champagne Tower, coming up.
Here comes the Tomoki Tower.
What's a Tomoki Tower?
The wait is over, ladies.
Gaze upon my manor.
This is the Tomoki Tower.
What?
What's wrong here, ladies?
Is there some kind of problem or a...
You jerk!
I hate you!
What happened?
I switched off the cool guy jamming.
Why did you do that?
Because I was busy helping out with your shop.
It was too much work keeping up with both.
No way.
But you have shown me what it's like to live the dream.
And I've finally got enough money.
I want to thank you for this, Nymph.
You're actually thanking me?
Yes!
And now I'm off to buy that DVD!
No.
Do not allow yourself to be led astray.
I'm an angeloid.
As long as I have this chain on my choker,
I'm destined never to disobey my master.
Your business venture is quite popular.
Why is it that you're forcing yourself to lie?
Who are you?
I am a human.
Why did Nymph return?
I do not know anything.
You know what it looks like to me.
Looks like you're saying the opposite of what you mean.
Normal humans lie, therefore I do also.
I am just like everyone else.
Very well, I see.
At this rate, Tomoki's going to end up quite sad.
Hey, Tomo! Over here!
Your timing's about perfect.
Why? What's going on?
We finally managed to figure out
what Icarus has been talking about all day.
At some point during the beginning of the day,
did you tell Icarus she should act more human?
Yeah, I don't know. Maybe.
Well, she certainly took it to heart
and has been trying her hand at lying.
You've been lying?
Everything you said was a lie then?
That means when you were saying how much you hated me,
you were actually telling me how much you love me.
Correct.
Everyone thinks you're cute.
Even though you seem violent,
underneath it all,
you're actually very nice and quite gentle.
So then that other thing you said?
How I'm too skinny?
Wait a sec.
Correct.
Which means I like that you're slightly overweight.
This also means there is a new world.
Correct.
And the Prez is a nice person.
I am nice, right?
Correct.
So that's that.
It was a lie when she said she didn't want to be with you anymore.
She simply reversed everything she was truly feeling.
Is she getting that right, Icarus?
Exactly.
Geez, don't scare me like that again, okay?
I thought you were gonna vanish on me too, like Nymph.
I can't believe you were just saying the opposite of what you meant.
You've changed quite a bit.
Remember, you didn't want them at all in the beginning.
Icarus and Nymph, I mean.
Well, I still don't want the trouble.
You know me, peace and quiet is the only way to live.
Just admit it already.
If you really want something to change, just change it.
Master, listen.
I want to tell you I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to cause so much trouble today.
It's cool.
I think I'm used to it.
Well then, do you mind if I ask you a question about something?
Huh?
When I tried so hard to lie to you about my feelings earlier, it caused me to think about how I really feel about you.
After a while, it started to bother me.
I need to know what you really think of me, Master.
Since I was little, no one's ever thought of me as normal.
I was a curious kid.
I wanted adventure in my life.
In a way, a large part of me wanted to be like Sugata.
One time, I found something cool in the mountains.
And I took the rest of my class up to see it.
Maybe I shouldn't have.
Because it was dangerous.
And one of my friends got hurt because I wasn't paying attention.
After that, nobody wanted to go up to the mountains with me anymore.
I think it was their parents who stopped them.
Something like that.
But the next thing I knew, I was all alone.
So that's why when I thought about you and Nymph vanishing on me like that, I guess I just got...
Well, it reminded me of what happened back then.
Master, I don't want to leave you.
I want to stay with you forever.
What the hell are you doing to me?
I'm trying to talk all serious about something, and it's like you're playing some crappy mind game on me.
What the hell is going on in that head of yours?
Everything's back to normal down here. For now, anyway.
Hello? I'm talking to you!
Thank you!
Well, thank you!
I ate my heartzinho
The first愛 nature likes it
My first love takes a diane
My cry Jean King
living into the school lap
A
video
a
The Age of Warring Boobs, G-Cup Rebellion, Tooth and Nail, Breast to Breast.
They're using those suckers like weapons!
You two have any idea what time it is?
What did I tell you about watching that?
Next time, where the melodious words of an angel go.
???
?
, ?